[
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "Anything that occupies space and has mass is called [BLANK].",
        "correctAnswer": "matter"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "Anything that occupies space and has [BLANK] is called matter.",
        "correctAnswer": "mass"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "Anything that occupies [BLANK] and has mass is called matter.",
        "correctAnswer": "space"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of [BLANK] properties matter is classified as solids, liquids and gases.",
        "correctAnswer": "physical"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of physical properties, [BLANK] is classified as solids, liquids and gases.",
        "correctAnswer": "matter"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of physical properties, matter is classified as [BLANK], liquids and gases.",
        "correctAnswer": "solids"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of physical properties, matter is classified as solids, [BLANK] and gases.",
        "correctAnswer": "liquids"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of physical properties, matter is classified as solids, liquids and [BLANK].",
        "correctAnswer": "gases"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of [BLANK] properties, matter is classified as elements, compounds and mixture.",
        "correctAnswer": "chemical"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of chemical properties, [BLANK] is classified as elements, compounds and mixture.",
        "correctAnswer": "matter"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of chemical properties, matter is classified as [BLANK], compounds and mixture.",
        "correctAnswer": "elements"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of chemical properties, matter is classified as elements, [BLANK] and mixture.",
        "correctAnswer": "compounds"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "On the basis of chemical properties, matter is classified as elements, compounds and [BLANK].",
        "correctAnswer": "mixture"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "The particles which make up [BLANK] are atoms or molecules.",
        "correctAnswer": "matter"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "The particles which make up matter are [BLANK] or molecules.",
        "correctAnswer": "atoms"
    },
    {
        "type": "fill-in-blank",
        "question": "The particles which make up matter are atoms or [BLANK].",
        "correctAnswer": "molecules"
    },
]
